iteleseminar.com 2018-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Instant Teleseminar

InstantTeleseminar.com is committed to protecting the privacy as well as the accuracy and security of information collected from our online visitors. This privacy policy is a statement of our guidelines and practices with respect to the collection, use, protection and disclosure of personal information acquired through your use of the website and online services. 

### Collection of Information

We collect information from online visitors who sign up for our services, ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. We collect this information from you to 1) establish and manage your account, including to provide notifications to you regarding your account; 2) to respond to your requests for support from us; 3) to inform you of newly-developed features or services and to solicit your adoption of these services; 4) to help us develop new services and features that meet your needs; and 5) to help you more fully utilize the service and its features, and 6) to bill and collect for services to satisfy InstantTeleseminar.com's legitimate business interests. 

We may request personally-identifiable information from you such as your name, billing, work, or home address, telephone number, e-mail address or credit card information. It is solely your choice whether or not you provide this personally identifiable information. However, should you choose not to provide the information, we may be unable to process an order, fulfill a service or display certain content on the Site. We do not sell or rent personal information, including personally identifiable information, to unrelated third parties. 

### Removal From Email List

You can choose to be removed from our email list at any time via a unique unsubscribe link sent with each email message, located at the very bottom or "footer" of the message. You may also be removed from our mailing list by contacting our support team at [support.instantteleseminar.com](https://support.instantteleseminar.com/), by emailing support@InstantTeleseminar.com, or by calling 503-290-5600. 

Removal from our mailing list may prevent you from receiving timely information which may directly or even negatively impact you or your business. These notifications may include maintenance windows, changes to the way service is delivered, and other messages important to the operation of your service. 

Removal from our mailing list only removes you from bulk notification messages. It does not remove you from all emails that may be sent to you from our domain, including automated billing notifications, emails from our support team and other employees and vendors, or any other transactional messages required to maintain service with InstantTeleseminar.com. 

### How to Access Your Personal Information

You have access to the information we collect from you via the website and you may correct inaccuracies we obtained from your registration. We require our customers to comply with applicable privacy laws and regulations pertaining to the use of our services. 

### Browser "Cookies"

Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive by various internet services which store information that help tailor the experience for your specific requirements. We may use cookies as a way of improving your experience with our service. Cookies do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Also, most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, though you can set your browser to refuse cookies. If your browser does not accept cookies, your InstantTeleseminar.com services may be disrupted, as many functions provided by InstantTeleseminar.com require cookies to fully operate. 

### Security

We utilize reasonable protections to ensure that personal information in our care is not misused or accessed without authorization. Personal information is stored on our own platforms or on the platforms of our service providers, with access restricted to those employees or contractors who have a need for such access to perform a legitimate business function relating to the services or for maintenance, internal security or related issues. 

### Third Party Web Sites

InstantTeleseminar.com's services may contain links to third party websites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of any third party websites. Before disclosing personal information to 3rd-party websites, we encourage you to review their specific privacy policies. 

InstantTeleseminar.com also uses third-party tracking and analytics to understand visitor traffic patterns, though this information is aggregated and not traceable to the end user by InstantTeleseminar.com. 

In the future, InstantTelesemianr.com may utilize third-party platforms such as Facebook, LinkedIn, or downloadable applications to mobile devices that allow us to access and/or collect certain information from that platform. You allow us to collect and access this information via this privacy policy as well as via the privacy policies provided by the third-party platforms. You also allow us to access information contained in cookies placed on your device by the Third Party Platform as permitted by the terms of your agreement and privacy settings with each specific Third Party Platform. We may share this information with the Third Party Platform for their use as permitted by the terms of your agreement and privacy settings with the Third Party Platform. 

We will share some of the information we collect from you with vendors and other service providers who work with us to support the internal operations of our website and/or mobile application for specific improvements to our services and feature set. 

### Consent

By submitting personal information to InstantTeleseminar.com or its affiliates and agents, you agree that we may collect, use and disclose such personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and as permitted or required by law. Your use of the InstantTeleseminar.com website and services signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. 

### Modifications

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the InstantTeleseminar.com website and service following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes. 

### Contacting Us

We can be reached by contacting: 

N Partners, LLC  
1712 Pioneer Ave Suite 1018  
Cheyenne WY 82001  

Email: support@InstantTeleseminar.com  
Phone: 503-290-5600
